<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Air PC</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">AIR PC</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">AIR PC</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="answer_to_what_are_we_measuring">We are measuring five pollutants: nitric oxide, nitrogen dioxide,
        carbon monoxide, ozone,and particulate matter. The NOx group (nitric oxide and nitrogen dioxide) is emitted from
        automobiles, power plants, and turbines. Carbon monoxide comes from automobile exhaust and burning fuel.
        Particulate matter is the result of a wide range of manmade and natural sources, while ozone is the
        result of reactions between chemicals already in our air. Together, these pollutants paint a comprehensive picture
        of air quality impacts from the interaction of human activity with natural processes.</string>
    <string name="description_co">What is it? Carbon monoxide (CO) is an odorless, colorless, and toxic gas that is often
        a byproduct of combustion in gas ranges, automobiles, or unvented kerosene heaters. CO can also be an important
        indoor pollution concern, because it is often produced from indoor heaters, chimneys and furnaces, fireplaces, and
        water heaters. \n \n
        Why does it matter? Because carbon monoxide is difficult to detect and might be a critical indoor pollution problem,
        our network is especially useful for CO detection. At low concentrations, it can cause mild chest pain in people with
        heart problems or fatigue in healthy people. CO can be fatal at high concentrations, because of its ability to limit
        oxygen intake in blood. Other potential issues include angina, impaired vision, and reduced brain function.</string>
    <string name="description_no">What is it? Nitric oxide (NO) is a byproduct of combustion of air in manmade systems such as
        automobile engines and fossil fuel power plants, or in natural processes such as thunderstorms. NO is a free radical
        (it has one unpaired electron), which means that it is highly unstable and likely rapidly reacts with surrounding gases.
        Usually, NO converts into nitrogen dioxide (NO2), which will enter a complex chain of reactions that may produce ozone
        or acid rain. \n \n
        Why does it matter? NO is not included in the Air Quality Index (AQI) produced by the Environmental Protection Agency.
        However, it is an important precursor to nitrogen dioxide (NO2), which is known to have detrimental effects on human
        respiratory health. NO2 can also likely produce ozone or acid rain.</string>

    <string name="answer_to_measuring_air_quality">Air quality is monitored in the United States by the Environmental Protection
        Agency (EPA), which determines air quality using a composite Air Quality Index (AQI). We devised our own AQI by adjusting
        for the unique measurement schemes calibrated on our sensor nodes. The index determines overall quality based on
        concentrations of fine particulate matter, carbon monoxide, and ozone. Concentrations are used to produce an index value,
        ranging from good to unhealthy.</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>
